Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Lieutenant Carapax.
tell me that
you've found the Scarab.
- They're cutting into it now.
- Ah. That's exciting.
I've had them working
around the clock
since we unearthed it
about two weeks ago.
Good.
Let's keep this thing airtight
until we're ready
to show the board.
Miss Kord. Miss Kord?
- Oh. Dr. Sanchez. hello.
- Sorry.
Hi. Actually.
that's not my name.
How much longer you think
it's gonna be?
We'll hit the center
before sunrise.
Well. push your men harder.
I've searched for 15 years.
I don't want
to wait another second.
Should've called before
making the trip out. Miss Kord.
This could be another decoy.
It's in there.
I can feel it.
All right.
Let's do this.
Excuse me. sir? How do I look?
Like you're six figures in debt.
Okay.
Anyone see him yet?
We say nothing for now.
Let's enjoy this moment.
Before he knows.
I'll tell him.
Are you crazy?
What the hell? Why not?
Even good news...
Sounds like bad news
when you deliver it.
And this is pretty bad news.
I can be joyful.
Your job is the balloon.
Hope I can handle it.
Handle what?
Hey. hey. hey!
The graduate is here!
- How was your flight?
- Good.
- Are you hungry?
- Of course.
Here. It's all they had.
- Welcome back. bro.
- Thank you.
Nana!
I'm so proud of you!
Finally together!
Now we hug!
Hey. where's Uncle Rudy?
Welcome back. pinche college boy.
Hey! Come on. Get out the car
and give me a hug.
No. No hugs. man.
They got Big Brother watching.
There's cameras.
I knew you were gonna
say something.
Facial recognition.
Body imaging scanners.
Yeah. and they're all so happy
to finally catch you.
You see? It's that kind
of talk right there
that's gonna get us all busted.
Where'd you get this?
I bought it for Jaime.
A boy? We know it's a boy.
There's probably a bug in here.
Come on. What are you doing?
Oh. my God!
I missed this so much.
Good to know
some things don't change.
Mom and Dad
have something to tell you.
- Milagro.
- What?
Okay. he's had his tacos.
now let him have the truth.
The truth? What is it?
- We...
We're losing the house.
What?
See?
- He didn't take it that bad.
- No. no. no. losing the house?
What does she mean.
losing the house?
- The landlord tripled the rent.
- They gave us three months
to come up with the money
or get out.
I am so sorry. flaquito.
No. Am don't be sorry.
It's not your fault.
It just means that
we're gonna have to
bust our ass at the shop. right?
Mmm... auto shop's gone.
- How?
- You can thank Kord for that.
- Brother.
- We couldn't keep up.
Especially since your dad. he...
He. uh... had a...
- He...
- Dad had a heart attack.
What?
I'm fine!
Just a clogged pipe
but I'm totally fine now.
At least the food's the same.
Wait. why didn't you tell me?
You were working so hard.
mi amor.
We didn't want
to distract you from school.
Ma. I could have done something.
I could have come back.
I could have been here.
I could have...
Animo. Jaime.
We figured it out.
We always do.
We have a lot
to be grateful for. Mira...
We're celebrating the first Reyes
to graduate from college!
Yeah. And the last!
Yes. because you didn't apply.
What. so I can get into debt
for the rest of my life?
No thanks.
What? 25%?
Mi amor.
these people make nothing.
We are broke.
Let's worry
about money tomorrow.
Remember how Mom taught us salsa
right there on the front porch?
You were always better than me.
Yeah. No. I
still think you don't know
how to dance salsa.
Yeah. I got
two left feet. I can't help it.
Yeah.
Do you remember
your 21st birthday?
I remember the first half.
I can't believe
we're losing this place.
It was rough.
Yeah. well.
I'm not leaving again.
What about grad school?
Well. that's not gonna
help the family.
I can't get us
into even more debt.
Animo. bro.
Okay. you always land
on your feet.
You're "Jaime."
Thank you. but...
This wasn't how it
was supposed to happen. Mili.
What was supposed to happen?
I was supposed to make it out.
I was supposed to get all of us
out of here.
Thanks. bro.
but I like the Keys.
- You know what I meant.
- Yeah.
Doesn't it bother you
that they talk about progress
and get everything
while we have to sit here
and go broke?
You're a Mexican
in Edge Keys. carnal.
That progress is not for us.
Okay? The poor go over here
and the rich go over there.
until the rich want to be here
and push us out.
We used to have the other side
of the tracks
and now they want that. too.
I still have a degree. right?
That's gotta mean something.
I'll get a job.
Not just any job.
but a prime job.
Yeah. I'm gonna get the money
to save this place.
Don't look at me at like that.
Look. Mili. I'm telling you.
in five years.
we're gonna be rolling in it.
This is just gonna be
one of our houses.
We're gonna have the mansion
on the water
with the marble everywhere.
infinity pool.
Yeah. just watch. Mili.
Just watch.
Excuse me. Mister Reyes?
You finish scraping the gum
off that lounger or what?
This is bullshit.
Wow. "Thanks. Milagro.
for hooking me up
with this gig."
It's not my fault your future
didn't turn out the way you wanted.
How am I supposed to
get experience
when nobody's gonna
give me a job?
Sounds like a "you" problem.
Seriously?
What? I'm keeping us employed.
you noob!
Yes. yes.
we've finally found it.
Doctor Sanchez
is running tests on it now.
- With the actual code in hand...
- Hey.
- We can move beyond the prototype phase.
- Check it out.
Yes. yes.
There goes Victoria Kord.
Look at that walk.
She's kinda sexy in like a...
Cruella Kardashian sorta way.
I don't think so.
- I'm gonna say hi.
- What? No...
Good afternoon. ma'am.
If you want. we could.
It's the breakthrough we've
been working towards. General.
Mm-hm.
We're invisible
to people like that. Jaime.
It's like our superpower.
Okay. Back to work.
I agree. That's a waste of time.
but General. I am telling you
what I'm gonna show
you tomorrow night
is gonna blow you away.
Yes. I look forward. also.
Bye.
Aunt Vicki?
Jennifer.
what are you doing here?
I didn't know you were coming.
Oh. Carapax.
this is Ted's daughter.
My favorite niece. Jennifer.
So. to what do I owe
this unexpected pleasure?
The world has changed.
Kord Industries faces
an unprecedented challenge
to secure our assets.
both here and abroad.
from our promethium mines
in Guatemala.
to our real estate developments
right here in Palmera City.
Introducing the future
of private policing:
The O.M.A.C..
the "One Man Army Corps."
Where are we going?
Gotta take a shit. bro.
Need you to be a lookout.
Wait. but the service restrooms
are out there.
Yeah. and I deserve a luxury
dump right now. all right?
Be my lookout.
I...
Using
revolutionary Kord symbiotech.
the O.M.A.C. connects directly
into the human brain.
to create a self-contained
war unit.
allowing a single soldier to
harness the power of legions.
The O.M.A.C. ensures security
Kord can rely on.
A future we can control.
The O.M.A.C.
Think it works pretty well.
don't you?
So. this... project
was shut down years ago.
Why have you relaunched it?
Jennifer. the O.M.A.C.
is the future of this company.
You should be so excited.
No. no. no. I really want
to know what's at Pago Island?
- That's classified.
- Mm.
It's a secret.
But I'll tell you.
what isn't classified
is what's gonna go on
at this party.
It's gonna be an amazing evening
with some
very interesting people.
so if you wanna come.
bring someone and it'll be fun.
All right. see you later.
I know what you're doing. Vicki.
We don't make weapons anymore.
Whoa. whoa. "we"?
Who's "we"?
You are nothing to this
company. You're an expense.
A brat in her daddy's
board seat.
jet-setting around the world
on the company's dime.
- doing your "charity work."
- My father would never...
Look. your father was handed
a company I built... my company.
Which he then proceeded
to almost sink
with his moronic inventions
and his reckless management.
and then after he'd done all
that. you know what he did?
He just disappeared.
and left me
to pick up the pieces.
Your father
abandoned this company.
And he abandoned you.
I won't let you do this.
Don't get in my way. Jennifer.
Back away.
I'm not afraid of you.
Maybe you should be.
Hey. hey!
Uh. sh... she said
to back away. ma'am.
Oooh-whee!
That was lavish!
Oh. shit.
And who are you. handsome?
Jaime Reyes.
I think it's time to find
a new job. Jaime Reyes.
- I'm...
- You. too. toilet. Go.
Andale.
Thanks.
Where's the car?
Uh. 47 minutes.
Hey. are you okay? That was...
I appreciate the chivalry.
but I can take care
of myself. okay?
Totally. But I mean...
what a dick. right?
She's a Kord.
They're all dicks.
Jenny Kord.
We're not all dicks.
- Obviously. Yeah. Uh...
- Uh...
Look I'm...
I'm really sorry about this.
It's fine.
Give me your phone.
Let me give you my number.
Okay. Yeah.
Yeah. Come by
Kord Tower tomorrow.
Okay.
I might be able to get you a job
somewhere else in our company.
Yes. Oh. my gosh.
That'd be great.
I'll do anything. Really.
Anything. huh?
Hey. you know
he has a degree. right?
- Pre-law.
- I... Yeah.
You guys need any pre-lawyers?
Okay.
- Text me.
- Okay.
Nice meeting you. Jaime Reyes.
Nice to meet you. too...
Jenny Kord.
I think she might be into you.
What? No.
Bye.
- You think?
- Yeah. Yeah.
She took one look
at your young Mexican-ass.
hero-of-the-moment vibe
and was into it.
Hey. you know what?
Maybe she'll pull you
out of poverty
- like Maria la del Barrio.
- Okay.
Except. she's
the rich white dude
and you're the Maria!
Yeah. Okay.
You drinking?
- Just one.
- Okay.
Don't tell your mother.
Can't sleep?
No.
I'm not sleepy either.
Yeah.
I planted those nopales with
la Nana.
when you were a baby.
Look at them now.
Like you and la Mili.
grown and beautiful.
You okay?
Yeah.
Sorry. Apa. it's just
everything right now
feels so out of reach. and...
I feel like I failed you guys.
We're on a journey. Jaime...
This house. the nopales.
el auto shop.
Everything.
They're just a stop
in the journey.
But this isn't the destination.
And what is it?
I don't know.
What's important is that
we go on this journey together.
Things don't last.
La familia. that's forever.
That lasts.
Don't look so sad.
Everyone has a purpose.
You just haven't found yours.
So what's your purpose then?
I'm still searching. too.
But right now. it's this.
Talking to you. right here.
See you in the morning.
Okay.
All right. okay. Jaime.
You got this.
God...
Thank you. Apa.
Ya. pues. you guys can go. okay?
You're gonna be okay. flaquito.
You belong here.
Yeah. cabezon.
You look like an asshole
just like everybody else here.
Come here!
I forgot to give you a blessing!
Okay.
- Bring your A-game. bro.
- Yeah.
Bring a Molotov cocktail
to burn this dump down!
Okay!
Hey. and get me a job. too!
Jaime. Jaime. Jaime...
They don't get out much.
Hello. I'm Victoria Kord.
and this is Kord Industries.
a company with the planet
in its sight
and the future on its mind.
We are taking our
cutting edge technology...
Hi. nice to meet you.
Deliveries are downstairs.
Uh... No. no. no.
My name is Jaime.
Jaime Reyes.
I'm here to see Jenny Kord.
Do you have
an appointment. Jamie?
- Um... It's Jaime. but...
- Sorry?
Uh...
Yes. I do have an appointment.
She said to drop by.
so I'm sure I should...
- Oh. you can stand there.
- Okay.
Why don't you
have a seat. Jamie?
Okay. Thank you.
She found it.
Jenny?
Uh... Okay...
Okay.
Just me and you.
No.
No. no. no. no. no. no. no...
No!
No. no. no. no. no!
There's been a security breach.
Lock the building.
Lock the building!
Jenny! Jenny.
What?
- Hey!
- Oh!
Jenny!
Oh... Sorry.
Hey. Jenny Kord!
It's me. Jaime from yesterday.
- I'm sorry. I'm in a rush.
- No. that's all good.
But you know. yesterday you
said you'd consider getting me a job
and. you know.
I can't leave without one
even if that sounds too...
Do you think you could pause
for one second? Please...
Look. Jaime.
this is really a bad time.
Okay. Let's... let's talk
while you have lunch.
Please...
Stay on comms.
You said you'd
do anything. right?
Yeah. Basically. anything.
Here.
- Guard that with your life.
- Okay.
But do not open it.
Do not touch it!
Don't even look at it!
Okay. I'm just gonna
guard it with my life.
Yeah. you're a quick learner.
- Yeah.
- Good. Now go!
- Okay. Okay!
- Go. go. go!
Lock up the south entrances!
You two. with me!
So. you went in to get us jobs.
and all you brought back
was a hamburger?
Okay. I don't think
it's a burger.
You haven't looked?
She said not to open it. I...
Oh...
- She's not here.
- What?
Open it!
Okay. okay. One look.
Oh. you guys are so childish.
What the hell is that?
Huh.
Looks like a bug. right?
Why was she hiding it?
I don't know.
Hm.
It's kind of a letdown.
The world's biggest tick.
Okay. You guys are the ones
who wanted to see it.
Hey. hey. hey!
Milagro. Okay. look. Very mature.
but she said to not open it. so please...
Mmm. she said for you
to not open it. bro.
Stop. stop. Hey. oye.
- It's heavy.
- Okay. okay.
I'm gonna use a motor.
all right?
- I'm gonna get my drill.
- Wait. wait!
Don't get the drill!
What are you doing?
God. I hate when you do that.
Whoa.
Ooh. Is that
the new Tamagotchi?
How did you get it to do that?
I don't know.
Ama.
I think it likes me.
What the hell!
It doesn't like me!
Jaime. it's on your face!
It's on your face!
Get it off!
Alberto!
Cabezon!
What the hell?
Where did it go?
Oh. man! I'm trying
to help you. cabezon!
I think it's inside of me.
Oh. my God! It's inside of me!
Inside you? How?
It went up his ass!
He's possessed!
Oh. my God.
Jaime!
Milagro!
Jaime! Jaime! Jaime!
Rudy. what's going on?
- He's moving. He's moving.
- Jaime?
No. no. no! No!
Damn! Shit.
That scared
the frijoles outta me.
Are you okay. mijo?
- Cabezon.
- Jaime.
Flaquito.
What the f...
Host acquired.
Who said that?
System
configuration initializing.
Wait.
You don't hear that?
Don't look at him in the eyes.
Analyzing host.
- Flaco?
- Mijo?
There's a voice in my head.
- Hello. Jaime.
- What is happening?
Begin systems check in three...
Systems check?
Two. one.
Thrusters engaged.
It's okay. It's gonna be okay!
What are you doing?
What's happening?
Escape
velocity protocol engaged.
Where are you taking me?
Crossing atmospheric layers.
Stop!
Adjusting
pressure for host protection.
Ay. virgencita. I'm in space.
I'm in space.
Oh. man. I'm in space.
What the hell is going on?
Wait. is that my house?
Testing re-entry systems.
Wait. wait. wait! No. no. no!
No. no. no. no!
Oh. my God!
Oh. my God. I'm on fire!
Stop. stop. stop! Oh. God!
Fly. fly!
No. No. no. no.
Approaching contact.
Oh. my God. I'm gonna die!
Three hundred meters.
Two hundred meters.
One hundred meters.
Braking systems check complete.
Oh. thank God it's over.
Okay. you can take me home now.
Flight systems engaged.
Wait. wait. wait...
Don't engage!
Stop. stop. stop!
Listen to me!
You've got the wrong guy!
I swear! I'm a nobody!
Oh. come on!
Testing acceleration systems.
Too fast! Too fast!
Watch out. watch out. watch out!
What was that?
I don't know what I'm doing!
Sorry about that.
Fine-tuning flight control.
Watch out. Watch out!
Pull up! Pull up!
Why are you doing this to me?
Host overreacting.
Overreacting? You kidnapped me!
How long ago did we take it?
20 minutes. I think.
- Man. has it hit you yet?
- No.
- 'Cause it ain't hit me.
- Man. has it hit you?
- Nah. man.
My back!
Landing systems check complete.
What was that?
- Are you guys okay?
- What did you do to my car. man?
Hey. hey.
do you have insurance. man?
Oh. I'm in so much trouble.
Threat approaching.
What the hell?
Oh. no. what did you do?
Host protection successful.
Hey. hey. look. is anyone hurt?
Oh. no. Calm down.
I can explain.
There's nothing to worry about.
Oh. my God. there's a kid!
It wasn't me. I swear.
This is gonna sound crazy.
but I'm not in control...
Systems check complete.
Oh. no. not again.
I think it just hit me.
Let me explain that again.
He's technically
not a missing person.
but he is missing.
- But also. he is...
- Possessed!
He exploded out of
the roof. With rockets on his back.
Shouldn't we be
out there looking for him?
No. no. no!
I'm on hold again.
Return landing successful.
Never mind. We found him.
Why are you naked?
Jaime?
Yo. put those huevos away. bro.
Just like when he was little.
Because he's cold!
Cover your balls. Jaime.
It's Jamie. not Jaime.
Oh. no.
What are you guys doing?
You okay?
He's alive.
Jaime. Do you feel okay. mijo?
Oh!
No. No way.
Jaime. listen.
- there's something on...
- No. not now. Milagro.
- Jaime. I'm serious.
- No. no. no. Not now. Milagro.
- Not now!
- There's something on your...
Hey. Jaime. keep that blanket
now that it touched
your chorizo.
What is going on?
You can't fly.
Superman can fly.
Those people on that bus
were okay. They're fine.
Okay. This probably
happens all the time.
Yeah. she wouldn't
do this to me.
Yeah. right. Okay.
I tried telling him.
Okay. guys. I... I need
to go find Jenny Kord.
'cause she's gonna know how
to get this thing out of me.
Uh. where are my shoes?
Come on. where are my... shoes.
Not the 84s!
These were my favorite shoes.
Okay. okay.
Jaime. what happened?
Where did you go?
Ama. I don't know.
I think I cut a bus in half
and then...
- Cut what?
- And flew into orbit.
- Flew into orbit?
- Apa. I don't know.
- That's why I need Jenny. Okay?
- I am calling the police.
No. no. Don't call the police.
No police. They work for Kord.
What do you think
Kord's gonna do
when they figure out
that some Mexican kid
has that type of military tech
inside of him?
They're gonna lock his ass up.
And then they're gonna
wipe our minds.
so that we don't tell anybody.
And it's not like
the government isn't
used to locking up
Mexicans anyway.
I mean. this is sci-fi shit.
This is CIA.
- This is Area 51!
- Rudy. focus. What do you mean?
What I'm saying
is the government and Kord
are gonna be all over this.
and then they're gonna
start asking for documents.
And that includes you. Nana.
And that includes you. Alberto.
Okay. then fine. I'm just gonna
have to go by myself then.
You are not leaving this house.
Ama. I'm 22! Besides.
what if she's in danger?
What if she's in danger?
- Jaime. you flew out of the roof.
- You don't understand.
- He's into her.
- Oh. he totally is.
- No. I'm not.
- Oh!
- Stalked her Insta.
- Where'd I put my...
She's Brazilian.
she lives at the Regent Tower.
And she's single. by the way.
Bit of a loner. though.
if you ask me. I mean...
She's single?
I thought you weren't into her.
What are you doing
with my phone?
You left it unlocked.
It's like Maria Mercedez.
Only she's the rich white guy
and he doesn't have a pot to piss in.
Yes. the Maria!
Yes. I said the same thing.
But Maria la del Barrio.
Even better!
I'm proud to say
I'm Jaime from the neighborhood.
He left his hometown
To make a living.
- You hear that. flaco?
- Rudy!
No. No. no.
No. No. No!
Jaime!
No! No! No!
Ma!
He took the Taco!
Don't be silly!
So itchy. this thing.
Ay. okay.
No way.
What the...
Wait. what?
Jenny?
- Oh. my gosh.
- What are you doing here?
- Just go. They're coming.
- Who's them?
Them!
- Oh. God. Okay!
- Let's go! Let's go!
Okay. okay! Oh. my God!
I told you to go!
You should have started with.
"they have guns."
Watch out!
Oh. Rudy's gonna kill me.
Oh. my headlights!
No! My mirrors!
What the hell. man?
What's wrong with you? Cabezon!
Do you want some water?
My tailgate!
No. I'm... I'm good. I'm fine.
Okay.
What did you do to the Taco?
And that... that's Rudy.
My name's Cesar. okay? And
only my friends call me Rudy.
- I'm Jenny.
- "I'm Jenny."
Hi. Jenny.
We know who you are.
What are you doing here?
Thinking about turning our
house into a nuclear power plant?
I went swimming out there
by where your family
has that company.
My testicles are seven times
their normal size.
Shouldn't you be
pillaging cobalt
from some developing country
or something. Jenny?
- Where is it?
- Yeah.
Allow me.
Rudy! What?
- What are you doing?
- Rudy!
I thought the
chingaderas would come out.
- Come out?
- Jeez.
- What is he talking about?
- He's talking about this.
Oh. I forgot how bad it looks.
Gross! Cover that up!
No. it doesn't look that bad.
You can barely see it.
I've seen worse.
- Where?
- You don't wanna know.
Okay. what the hell
is this thing?
It's... it's called the Scarab.
It was given to my dad
when I was a kid. um...
It's some kind
of a world destroying weapon.
Oh. that's nice.
- Weapon?
- What did she say?
What?
And did you know what was
gonna happen to my brother
when you stuck him with
this world destroying thing?
No. I swear to you. I had
no idea this would happen.
I mean. come on.
My father said it can't be
activated by just any person.
It has to choose you.
So I'm guessing it's chosen you.
No more blind dates.
Okay. So. how do we get it
to un-choose me?
I don't know.
But we better move fast.
because my aunt will kill
us all just to get it back.
Kill us?
No. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that.
She's the one who sent
the assassins.
Yeah.
Like the assassins in Mexico?
I'm so sorry I
put you all in this situation.
I had no idea it would activate.
Really. I didn't know.
That's convenient.
But she already said
she didn't know.
She's a Kord. dude.
You seriously trust her?
We are going
to figure it out. We always do.
Come on. we are the Reyes.
We've dealt with harder things.
We have?
Animo. We can do this.
Yeah. Yeah. Apa.
He's right.
Okay. so. how are we gonna
get this thing outta me?
You know. before it busts
another hole in our house.
Exactly.
There's a place where
we can get some answers.
But we need the key.
Okay. so where's the key?
At the Kord building.
And they're probably on high alert
over there since I took the Scarab.
So. what are we talking about?
Laser-based security system?
Wide area motion imagery?
Maybe. uh... photonic emitters?
I really don't...
Because I've been working on
something that I believe can help us.
And it's almost finished.
If I can get
the mechanical structure right.
Mm. I love you. Ma.
Give me a couple hours.
You're aware
that if you deliver the O.M.A.C..
you'd be the most powerful
weapons manufacturer
in the world.
If you buy into this. you can
call me whatever you want.
Oh. if it isn't
the devil himself.
General.
this is Lieutenant Carapax.
He's been crucial to the
development of the prototype.
and I personally handpicked him
for his courage
during the anti-communist
counter-terrorism operations
in Guatemala.
He's the perfect recipient
for the O.M.A.C..
and a product of the school
of the Americas.
Great to meet you. Lieutenant.
Well. can't wait to see it
in action.
- When will it be ready?
- Oh. it's ready. isn't it?
We're just putting some
finishing touches on it.
We have a problem.
Well. if you'll excuse us.
Have a cigar.
they're made by real Cubans.
You lost her? How?
My men saw someone helping her.
All right. I wanna find out
who she is working with now.
Because without the Scarab.
we can't complete the O.M.A.C.
I'm on it.
I will bring the Scarab back.
This time I'll do it personally.
Well. I would hope so.
Carapax. because if not.
all your sacrifices
will have been in vain.
Just think of how much suffering
your body has been through.
I'm aware
of what you've done to it.
My God... What we've done.
Ignacio. I'm on your side.
Do you not remember what
it was like when I found you?
How badly crippled you were?
How broken?
I am just trying to fix you.
Okay?
Good.
I have to go back to the party.
Now. go get me that Scarab.
That's it?
I call it. El Chapulin.
Why?
You know.
when you make something cool.
you can call yours
whatever you want. okay?
Here. be useful. Hold that.
You're sure that this one works?
Thank you. Yes.
Unlike the junk that Kord
makes. my tech delivers.
Okay. You could have
just said yes.
Okay. cupcake. you wanna
hit that yellow switch there?
Hit the yellow switch.
I just did.
Okay.
Well. at least I don't have to
open that annoying tailgate.
It's going on your tab.
So just give me. like. one step.
Just gotta give it a little...
- Oh. that's sexy.
- Great.
That's... that's great.
Uh. so it works.
Uh. yeah. it works.
I'll keep the truck running.
- Let's go.
- Wow.
"So it works?"
Guys!
Something's happening.
What the hell is this?
El Chapulin Colorado!
So join me and my little pals
and all of our Kord
subsidiaries...
The key's here.
Around the globe.
to build a better future.
A Kord future.
She seemed so different
back then.
Vicki and my grandfather
started Kord Industries together...
and turned it
into a military powerhouse.
Then. when my grandfather died.
Victoria thought the company
would go to her.
But he left everything
to my dad instead.
- Seems kind of...
- Sexist?
Yeah.
Still. my father wanted
to steer the company
in a different direction.
So. Victoria became obsessed
with erasing my father's legacy.
Could I get a hand over here?
Yeah. sorry. What do you need?
- Just hold this.
- Okay.
There's a signal blocking
our feed.
We're being jammed out.
Lieutenant Carapax?
We got a problem.
- This is the key?
- Yeah.
Okay. let's go.
Let's go.
This is why I
don't let anyone drive the Taco!
To be honest. I didn't
think the Chapulin would work.
Yeah. that's Rudy.
He's like the Mexican Doc Brown.
No kidding. Okay.
- So that's all you need?
- Yeah.
Oh. my God.
I don't know why I thought
it was gonna be
way harder than that.
Oh. shit.
The Scarab. now!
What is he doing here?
Should we run?
He's not slowing down.
Watch out! Watch out!
Hola. Jaime.
Oh. my gosh. How'd you do that?
I have no idea.
Oh. he's pissed.
What the hell is that thing?
The O.M.A.C.
You're going to regret that.
Defending host.
Oh. my God. Quick!
Go find Rudy!
Engaging
threat. Engage? No!
Oh. shit!
Okay. wait. wait. wait!
No. no. no. wait! Don't!
What did you do that for?
I told you not to engage.
I have
an arsenal at my disposal.
No! No weapons.
Ooh. And my song. too! Ay!
- Cesar!
- What?
- What the heck. where's cabezon?
- There!
Hey! Calm down!
Oh. shit!
- Let's go. let's go. let's go.
- Let's go. let's go!
Let me talk to him.
Verbal
communication is ill-advised
in a combat scenario.
Hey. man. look! I think this is
just one big misunderstanding...
I didn't mean
to punch you back there.
I promise. I would never...
I'm not
in control of this thing.
No. no. no. let me explain!
Never mind. He's not listening.
Permission to take over host.
Yes! Anything!
Watch and learn. Jaime.
Hey. wait. where you going?
Come on.
What the hell?
Oh. my God. My hands are guns.
Threat neutralized.
Oh!
What's with the blades?
Eliminating threat.
No. no. no.
Put the blades away.
Would you
like to use a different weapon?
No. I mean.
we don't have to kill him.
Eliminating threat.
Are you even listening to me?
Stop! I'm not a killer.
Command accepted.
Oh!
Cabezon!
Jaime!
Uncle Rudy.
No!
Holy shit!
Rudy!
Where do you think you're going?
Hey! You guys
gotta get out of here!
What's with this guy?
What?
Stupid boy.
Did you think you could beat me?
Recommend lethal measures.
I told you. I'm not a...
Warning.
host concussion detected.
You should have finished me
when you had the chance.
He's gonna kill him.
No. He's not.
Hold on.
Please. just don't
hurt my family.
The love you feel
for your family
makes you weak.
Cesar! What are you doing?
Okay. Kord girl.
When I tell you. pull that
handbrake and pull it hard.
- You ready?
- Oh. my gosh. this is insane.
Three. two. one.
Now!
Cabezon. let's get outta here!
Is he okay? Jaime! Jaime!
Jenny! Snap out of it!
- Okay.
- Don't look. don't look!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm fine. Rudy. Thank you.
All right. I got a T-shirt.
On the side.
All right. Okay.
Man...
Oh. that psycho
almost killed me.
You got the key?
- All right.
- Yeah.
Good. Now. let's go get
that Scarab taken out of you.
- Khaji-Da.
- Khaji que?
The Scarab's name is Khaji-Da.
How do you know?
I... Something happened
back there. My...
It's like I feel it in my mind.
Is that crazy?
You're becoming symbiotic.
- What?
- Okay. where to now?
- Take that exit.
- What? Hold on!
No. no. no!
Does anybody in
this town know how to drive?
Oh!
They're not gonna
look for you here?
No one's been here
since I was eight.
Yeah. I get it.
That makes sense.
So. your dad was all
obsessed with Scarabs. huh?
Where are we?
No way.
Wait.
Ted Kord was Blue Beetle?
Wow!
What the hell is Blue Beetle?
Oh. you were a kid.
It's like Palmera's superhero.
Like Superman in Metropolis
or the Flash in Central City.
But just. uh...
I don't know.
maybe just not... not as good.
I can't believe
he was the Blue Beetle.
Oh. I get it though.
Eccentric billionaire. a
genius. El Escarabajo Azul.
Your dad was a great man.
I had no idea.
You can call me Cesar or Rudy.
You can call me whatever
you want. I don't care.
Hey. how come all of this...
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Um. what were you saying?
Yeah. how come this stuff
doesn't look more like...
Nicer? Less ridiculous?
No. But I mean...
Like. look at this. It's
like Batman's stuff. but...
like if he had ADHD
or something.
Batman's a fascist.
The Blue Beetle.
he had a sense of humor.
My dad was never able
to unlock the Scarab.
So instead. he built his own
tech to fight as Blue Beetle.
If there's a way to get it out.
it's in there.
Let's crack into this sucker.
- Damn. you stink.
- This is your shirt.
Come on. I think there's some
of my dad's clothes upstairs.
That's a good idea.
This is gonna take a minute.
Jeez.
When is this day gonna end?
Whoa.
Ay.
Is everything okay?
Um. yes. Yeah.
Yeah. I'll be right out.
Yeah. I think they. uh...
I think they fit.
And they're comfy. too. so...
Good.
It must have been so cool
growing up in a place like this. no?
Honestly. it was...
it was pretty lonely
most of the time.
It was just you three in here?
Yeah.
That was my mother's
last painting.
Why'd she stop?
My mom died when I was six.
Oh... We don't...
- I'm so sorry to...
- It's okay. No. it's okay.
It's fine.
What was she like?
She was great.
She changed my dad's life.
She was the one who taught him
that the world
is a place to protect.
Nice.
But when my mom died. he...
he really went adrift.
He obsessed over the Scarab
and he would disappear for days.
Sometimes weeks.
And one day. he...
he left and...
didn't come back.
I'm so sorry. Jenny.
You're really lucky.
This house is...
it's full of stuff.
Your house is full of love.
A family.
Yeah.
That's a home.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Sorry for... for what?
I... I haven't talked about
this in a very long time.
Kinda feels nice to.
maybe. right?
Thank you.
Yeah.
You're a good listener.
My mom says it's 'cause
I got big ears.
Hey. guys.
I found something that... Ho!
- Nothing happened.
- Her mom died.
I found something you guys
need to look at.
Uh. great.
That's great. Let's go.
Nice jammies. guey.
Okay.
I've gone through the files.
So... Ted had a professor.
this guy named Dan Garrett.
The Scarab chose
this Garrett guy
before it chose you. Jaime.
And pinche Ted.
ran tests on him to map out
how the Scarab would react
to the human body.
So. once this Scarab
goes up someone's ass...
It didn't go up my ass.
Okay. Well. it connects
to the brain
and that's what it's trying to do to
you. Jaime. connect to your brain.
It's trying to become one
with you.
Why?
I think you should
ask it yourself.
I mean. this thing
has its own will.
It's sentient.
That's why it chooses a host.
That's why sometimes. it does what
you want. and sometimes. it doesn't.
Okay. well. who made it?
Can they help us?
This wasn't made
on Earth. cabezon.
- No way.
- Si way.
It's alien.
Yeah. I don't really like
the term "alien."
- You can use it. but I just...
- Whatever. Rudy. Come on.
What happened to Ted's
professor guy? How did he get it out?
You might want to sit down.
- Or not. All right...
- Rudy. please. Focus.
I got good news
and I got bad news.
The good news is. I
figured out how to get it out.
Fine.
And the bad news is
that you have to be dead.
- What?
- Dead.
What do you mean "dead"?
Okay. right now. Jaime. look.
It's fusing itself
to every cell in your body.
It's completely coiled
around your brain.
And there's nothing on earth
that could remove it.
It's designed
to protect its host.
To keep it alive.
So you're saying that
this thing's in me forever?
No. it's not forever.
I mean. it's just until you...
until you die.
I think it's kinda cool.
No. I mean. basically.
you are a superhero. cabron.
I'm so sorry.
I had no way of knowing...
Oh. you had no idea. So
then what are my options now?
So. option one is
to become an android
for the rest of my life.
Or option two is to hand myself
over to a murderous
- billionaire psychopath?
- I'm so sorry.
All I wanted was a job.
- Maybe there's a...
- Maybe what. Rudy?
It's all bad news.
Okay. this shit just doesn't
get any better for us.
I don't understand
why you can't...
God.
Whatever. I'm gonna...
I'm gonna go for a walk.
Jaime. just...
Let me go talk to him. I
think I know where he's going.
Cabezon. wait up.
God.
There he is.
I knew I'd find you out here.
Like a cat. Jaime.
I'm sorry
for yelling at you. Rudy.
I shouldn't have yelled at you. but...
It's not lost
on me that your situation
is a little bit
out of the ordinary.
Yeah. we're...
we're resilient people.
Life will continue to hit us
with curve balls. and...
difference is. when we
get hit. we get stronger.
Look at your old man.
He brought me here from Sonora.
I was ten. I think he was 19.
And people think
crossing the border is hard.
Yeah. it's hard.
but you know what's harder?
The next 20 years after.
I mean. la chinga.
But your viejo would work
16 hours a day. bust his ass.
Any ja he could
get his hands on.
Jornalero. bus boy. waiter.
He was a mechanic.
era de todo. dishwasher.
And to get us all
here and to keep us all together.
And not that he wanted to.
he had to.
That's what we come from.
The universe has
sent you a gift. Jaime.
And you have to figure out
what you're going to do with it.
Maybe this did all happen
for a reason.
Maybe it's time
that we get our own hero.
And not just some
foot up our ass.
Hey. but what do I know. huh?
I'm just some failed promise
that sleeps
in his brother's living room.
Don't say that. man.
You're not a failed promise.
Come on. you're the shit!
You know it.
- I am the shit.
- Yeah.
And... and I love you.
And I love you. too. cabezon.
Yeah. all right.
Guys?
Do you hear that?
That's Victoria.
Where are they going?
Home.
You're wasting too much water.
It's always my fault.
Yeah.
Something wrong?
Guys?
I think there's somebody
at the window.
Jaime Reyes.
come out with your hands up.
Turn yourself in.
We are authorized
to use deadly force.
Jaime Reyes.
come out with your hands up...
Get away from the windows!
We are authorized
to use deadly force.
Okay. Okay.
Um...
I'm gonna fly. I'm gonna fly.
Let's do this.
Yeah!
Yeah. no chance.
Now!
- Ay!
- Dude. no worries.
- Just take your time.
- Thanks. Jenny.
- You gotta force it to come out.
- What do you...
Oh. Oh.
- You're a genius.
- I know. What'd I say?
You said this thing's
gonna protect me. right?
- I...
- It's not gonna let me die?
No. no. I mean. when you die...
- All right. let's see if it works.
- I wouldn't test it.
- No. no. no. Jaime!
- Wait. wait. wait. Jaime!
Well. back to the Tacoma.
I guess.
Yeah.
We have the Reyes
house surrounded. The family's inside.
You know what to do.
Round them up!
Breach team. go.
On me.
We're in!
Fan out. Flash!
Clear!
- Get the light on.
- I got your left!
Back room. clear!
Clear!
Hands
on your head. Don't move.
- Okay. okay.
- Don't move!
- Don't touch my family!
- Get up!
Let's go! Up. up!
Hands up! Watch your two!
Miss Kord. we found the family.
We got 'em coming
out. Take 'em out.
Let's go.
Drag them out!
Come on! Let's go. come on!
- Let her go!
- Move. move!
Let's go. let's go!
Let's go!
Do not resist!
No! No! No!
Get
on the ground. On the ground!
Get down. now!
Let's go. now!
The kid's not there.
Find him!
Is he inside?
Don't say anything.
Where is he?
I could use
that arsenal right about now.
Thought you'd never ask.
Hell yeah!
Nice work. Khaji.
You guys okay?
- Jaime?
- Sorry. I'm late. Mom.
Magnificent.
Wait. what?
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
Look. don't shoot.
I don't wanna hurt you guys.
Fire!
God damn it!
I said don't shoot.
Oh. my God. I'm bulletproof.
Let's see what you can do.
Target the family.
- Engage.
- Take 'em out.
I got you guys.
Don't worry.
It's gonna be okay.
Okay. let's see what you got.
Eliminating threats.
What? No. Khaji. no killing.
Yeah. that's more like it.
Get out of here.
Run!
Analyzing threat level.
Okay. Let's do this.
Hell yeah!
Down on the ground!
- Papi!
- Mili!
We got one.
Hide!
Stay down. Don't move.
Stay where you are.
- No!
- We got another one.
Dad!
Come to papa.
Carapax. ready the claw.
Daddy. I'm scared.
Everything is gonna be okay.
- Jaime. your family.
- Stay down!
Okay. come on. Papi.
Mili. get Dad outta here. Go!
- Go!
- Okay. Okay. let's go.
Ready.
They have a weapon.
I suggest we retreat.
No way. They attack my family.
we're gonna finish this.
And...
Dad.
Dad. no. Dad. what's wrong?
Dad! Dad!
No. no. no! Dad!
No!
No. no. no.
- Dad!
- No!
Now!
Now. what's happening?
- Symbiotic systems...
- Khaji. do something!
Dad. no!
Dad! Apa!
- Apa!
- Jaime!
No. No. no. no.
No.
No. Jaime.
Jaime. watch out!
You! You!
What do you want with us?
- Dad. no!
- What are you doing?
Get this thing off of me.
you psycho!
Mom!
- Mami!
- Mili!
Alberto!
Alberto.
Let me go!
- Khaji. do something!
- I got him. Let's go.
Apa!
- Rudy. Rudy. Rudy.
- Wake up.
Apa!
I'm gonna come...
I'm gonna come get you.
Call an ambulance.
Clear!
Clear! Clear!
We have to help Jaime.
Mm?
We don't have time for self-pity.
We must rescue Jaime.
That's what his father would have wanted.
Listen...
I know how you feel
but we have to be brave.
There will be a time to cry.
This is not that time.
We have turned both cheeks.
Now is the time to fight.
Nana is right.
Mili. We have to go and save Jaime.
How? Okay. we don't even
know where they took him.
I might know where he is.
Please.
Come with me.
I can help.
Watch your step.
All right.
Let's do this.
Let's go.
Okay. okay.
I'm done. I'm done.
Okay. guys.
Let's hope this Kord tech works.
Hang on.
Okay...
Dude!
- There.
- Welcome back to the Bug Ship. Teddy.
Oh. that's sexy.
Look at you.
- This is sick.
- Thrusters!
- Let's go get our boy.
- Let's do this.
Jenny.
Okay. Good. good.
good. Good.
So. what's
the plan when we get there?
We'll burn that bridge
when we get to it.
That's not how you say...
Ama. I'm flying!
Whoo!
After 15 years.
everything we've done.
every sacrifice we've made.
has led to this moment.
Finally. the power
of the Scarab will be ours.
Almost there.
We are going
to change the world. Carapax.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
This will make you feel better.
Is this thing bulletproof?
We'll need more than a flying bug
to save Jaime.
Well. do you guys
wanna see Dad's toys?
Wait. is that
Kabloom bubble gum?
Oh. no. no. That's
not what you think it is.
It's just a special prototype
my dad was designing for me
when I was little.
Do these things work?
Mm... some of them.
Sometimes.
Whoa.
Oh. that's the Bug Shield.
Try pressing another button.
Yeah. you know what?
I think I'm keeping this one.
Okay. so. how are we
supposed to learn
how to use these things?
Nana?
Hey. How do you know
how to hold that so perfectly?
There's plenty you don't know
about your Nana.
This is where they took Jaime.
Pago is a Caribbean island
off the coast of Cuba
that Kord bought from Batista
in the 50s.
The place is a fortress.
Okay. how the hell
are we gonna get in there?
I've stormed this kind of fortress before.
What the hell?
Mili. one day. we gonna
have to talk
about Nana's revolutionary past.
Her what?
Let me see that tunnel.
That's how we get in.
We will create a diversion
while they go in
directly to the basement.
Yeah. the generators are here.
- Mm.
- We could blow them up
and knock power out.
After that. you go and find Jaime.
We'll be the getaway.
Any questions?
Hm?
Damn. Nana.
Hey. who are you?
What're you doing? Get
me out of this thing. please?
Is there a problem. Sanchez?
I'm sorry.
You're sorry? You're sorry?
What does that even mean?
Tell her to get me out of this!
It's okay. It's okay.
Yeah. Listen. kid.
The Scarab chose you.
that's true.
But it doesn't belong to you.
It belongs to me.
But now that you've
activated it.
we can transfer its code
directly into the O.M.A.C.
What are you even talking about?
No. no. Miss Kord.
It could kill him.
Oh. bummer.
Well. but sacrifices have to
be made for the greater good.
And this is yours. Jaime Reyes.
Do it. Sanchez.
With all due respect.
my name. again. is not Sanchez.
Hey. hey!
Get me outta this thing!
Damn it.
Bug.
- Rudy.
- Yeah. I see it.
You're going too fast!
Here goes nothing.
Hold on. hold on!
All right. All right.
Incoming!
Brace for impact!
Let's go. let's go!
On the wall! Engage. Engage.
Rudy. do something.
Rudy. we need to move.
We need to move.
Here we go!
Whoa.
Okay. okay.
Get out of the way. Sorry!
- It's like I can't miss.
- Right there. right there.
I stepped on him!
- Twenty points!
- Whoo-hoo!
Activating cloaking system.
Activating bug fart.
Take that!
Whoo!
- Yeah. this way.
- Okay.
Hey! Come on.
I know you can hear me.
Just let me out!
I'll keep it safe.
Start the transfer.
And when it's complete.
kill the kid.
Get me out of here!
But. Miss Kord.
we could learn so much
from his connection
to the Scarab...
We can learn a lot more
if we take it off his corpse.
Let me out! No! No!
Milagro. here. hide!
Holy shit.
Okay. I think we're good.
What the...
Victoria. you crazy bitch.
What the hell is this?
Fully operational
O.M.A.C. systems.
Enough to build an entire army.
Miss Kord. this...
this isn't looking good.
What's going on?
Oh. no.
The Scarab download
is generating too much power.
Our systems are spiking.
What does it mean?
The transfer is killing him.
He can't die before
the transfer is completed.
His pulse is dropping.
Well. just fix it!
Hey. flaco.
Dad.
What's going on?
What are you doing here?
You know.
No. Apa.
Everything is going to be okay.
Milagro. here.
Help me with these.
Jaime.
This is not your time.
You have to go back.
Come with me.
Please.
I understand everything now.
My destiny was
to be here with you.
In this moment.
To help you cross into it.
The universe knows it's you.
I know it's you.
You know it as well.
This is your purpose.
The scarab has chosen you for a reason.
It's time for you
to accept your destiny. Jaime.
How am I gonna
do this without you?
I'll always be with you.
How am I gonna know what to do?
All the answers are here.
I love you. son.
I love you. too. Papi.
Something's happening.
What?
His brainwaves. they're syncing
with the Scarab's frequency.
Right there.
They're connecting.
I need you. Khaji!
They're becoming one.
We've got the code?
The transfer's complete.
The code is ours.
It's working!
Oh. no.
Go. go. go!
Okay. Here we go.
- Okay. let's go.
- Yeah.
No. No. no. no.
Sanchez. stop him!
Oh. shit.
What?
Get your family
and get off this island. okay?
- Wait. wait. wait. My family?
- Quickly!
What do you mean my family?
Go!
Sanchez. you moron.
What are you doing?
My name is not Sanchez. pendeja!
It's Jose Francisco Morales
Rivera de la Cruz!
What are you doing?
Stop him. Carapax.
Go. I'll be fine.
Okay. Khaji. come on.
Okay.
All right. Khaji. activate!
Rebooting.
Rebooting? Are you kidding me?
Oh. God. Oh. no. Oh. no.
- Go. go. go.
- Okay. okay. okay.
Milagro. wait.
- Oh. no. no. no.
- What's wrong? What's wrong?
No. no. watch out!
Jenny.
Jenny?
Jenny!
Finally. I can feel it.
Oh...
Now this look really suits you.
Okay.
Okay. Khaji.
All right. Khaji-Da.
You got this. You can do this.
Come on! Let's go! Let's go!
Still rebooting.
Come on!
Freeze!
Stay right there!
Come on.
Don't move.
Take him down.
Nana?
Come on.
Okay.
Where did you learn
to shoot like that?
I'll tell you later.
Keep your eyes peeled.
Down with the imperialists!
Now we can go.
Milagro!
Jennifer. Jennifer. Jennifer.
What a mess you have made.
Let's go.
On your feet. Get up!
Ama.
You ok?
Yeah.
Sheez.
- Milagro.
- Where is she?
Milagro and Jenny.
They're in there.
Oh. you gotta be kidding me.
Okay. I need to head
back in there. okay?
Yeah.
What about the suit?
It's not working right now.
I can't deal with it.
- Jaime.
- Yes?
Okay.
Uh... Rudy. what's
that chongo thing called again?
Khaji-Da.
Right.
I know you can hear me.
Khaji-Da.
I want you both
to get it together.
Find your strength. mijito.
Use the pain we're feeling
and turn it into power.
I want you
to go back in there...
And kick their asses!
I found one of them.
Sick.
- Drop your weapon.
- Oh. goddamn it.
Hey! Pendejos!
Rebooting complete.
Get the hell away
from my sister.
- I'm out.
You ready Khaji?
Let's kick their ass.
Come on. let's get it.
Who's first?
Oh. you want some?
Wait. wait. wait! Watch out!
Engage the target.
Let's go!
Oh. man. there's more.
Grab him!
What the hell?
Get 'em off of me!
With pleasure.
- Thanks. Khaji.
- De nada.
Halt!
One more left.
Get over here!
Come on.
Nice slap.
Where were you?
Okay. I deserve that one.
I thought
I'd never see you again.
I told you I wasn't
going anywhere.
- Well. you did.
- Yeah. that wasn't my...
Rudy! Rudy!
Mili. oh. my God. Oh. my God.
You're safe.
I thought I lost you.
No. no. Look.
Hey. hey. hey.
Wait. wait. wait.
Where's Jenny?
We got separated. I don't know.
Okay. we have to find her.
Okay. we're gonna find her
before the others do because I...
Watch out!
What the hell was that?
O.M.A.C. incoming. Jaime.
Ah. crap.
Get off!
Okay. let's do this. Khaji!
Give me rockets or something.
Deploying blasters.
Okay. now give me blades.
Okay. now give me...
Careful.
he's stronger than before.
Okay. I get it.
Okay. which way do we go?
Go to the Bug Ship.
It's that way.
- But where are you going?
- I'm gonna get Cabezon. Go!
Critical wing damage.
Scratch my back?
Well. I'll scratch yours.
All right. big boy.
You do not deserve this power!
I thought you'd
hit harder than that.
Okay. we need
something else. Khaji.
Accessing energy reactor.
There we go.
All right. you wanna dance. huh?
Now. give me a sword.
So I can make whatever
weapons I want. huh?
Whatever
you can imagine. I can create.
Let's party.
Nice choice.
Let's go!
Home run! Whoo!
Oh. yeah!
Come on.
That's all you got?
Let's not
get ahead of ourselves. Jaime.
Khaji. don't worry.
We got this.
Okay. this is a little
harder than I thought.
Regenerative systems critical.
What the hell?
There can only be one of us.
Khaji. do something!
What's wrong?
Can't breathe?
Jaime.
I cannot protect you anymore.
I'm sorry.
Khaji. Khaji. stay with me.
You are still
a scared little boy.
I told you.
the love you feel
for your family...
makes you weak.
Hey!
Take these!
Come on!
Come and get me.
Rudy.
Oh. shit.
No!
Rudy!
Khaji-Da!
Your O.M.A.C. has failed.
Jennifer. you don't know
what the O.M.A.C. is.
Carapax is just a prototype.
This is the only thing
that's important.
The Scarab code.
With this. I can make
a thousand Carapaxes.
This is the culmination
of my life's work.
This is the Kord legacy.
This is our legacy.
Not mine. I'll make sure of it.
You're... you're gonna side
with that Edge Key trash
over your own family?
That Edge Key trash...
knows more about
family than you ever will.
I know. No. I know
about family.
I know about my family
that overlooked me.
just the way that you are now.
because you are
just like your pathetic father.
who didn't have the guts
to do what was necessary
for the greater good.
I wish that Ted were here now
to see this.
Me too.
Oh!
No! We're not done!
Jaime. threat disarmed.
You're losing control.
You think
that you could beat me? Huh?
You should have finished me
when you had the chance!
O.M.A.C. neutralized.
Recommend to disengage.
What are you doing?
We are not killers. Jaime.
Let him go.
What about Dad?
What about Rudy?
During the transfer.
I unlocked his memories.
Let me show you.
What if he doesn't
survive the procedure?
Then we'll just get another one.
It could kill him.
Sacrifices must be made
for the greater good.
This country is
confronting a brutal challenge.
from guerrillas
armed and supported
by others outside Guatemala.
The United States is
committed to restoring democracy
and to address the root causes
of the violent insurgency.
We know about the problems
confronting Guatemala.
Perfect. Round them up.
Mama!
Ignacio!
Do you understand now?
Hey! Cabezon!
You're wrong.
That love that
I have for my family...
that's what makes me strong.
All right. give it to me.
Come on.
- This?
- Yes. that.
No!
Now what have you done?
No! No. no!
Jenny?
It's okay.
Carapax. kill them.
Kill them both!
Take care of your family.
Go.
Okay.
What are you doing?
They're getting...
Okay.
No.
Wait. Jenny. wait.
Go back to the Bug Ship.
I'll be right behind you.
- What?
- I promise.
We can be partners. huh?
I'll f... I'll fix it.
I'll fix you.
We can find another Sanchez.
Do you remember everything
that I've done for you?
I remember everything now.
No.
Khaji. what's he doing?
He's maxing out
the energy reactor in his suit.
I advise we back away.
Ignacio.
It's time...
What? What?
What. no! What are you doing?
Stop! No! No!
Time to come home.
Sacrifices must
be made for the greater good.
No! Please! No!
Ignacio. no! Stop!
I suggest we run.
Okay. Oh. shit.
Milagro. pull!
Rocio!
You okay?
Hi.
Mili.
Cabezon.
Rudy?
Rudy!
- How?
- Yeah. You know...
Bad weed never dies.
Ama.
Nana.
Now we can cry.
It is a delicate moment
for Kord Industries.
And of course. we mourn
the loss of Victoria Kord.
But I'm looking forward.
As I was saying.
we will no longer make weapons.
What I want to do is honor
my father's legacy.
It's not about destruction.
it's about building
a better future.
It's not about taking
from the community.
but giving back
to the community.
What are we gonna do now?
Animo. Rudy. okay?
We're gonna get through this.
we always do.
Hey! The Reyes are here.
Guys.
Everybody showed up.
Nana.
Okay.
Now we can start to rebuild.
Where. Ama?
We don't have a house.
Rudy. we have. like. half the
Edge Keys in our yard right now.
I'm sure they'll be happy
to help us out.
Of course they're going to help.
Yeah. until when?
Until Kord pushes us out?
I wouldn't worry about that.
Jenny. Jenny.
Hi.
Thank you for coming.
I think it's time
to return the Edge Keys
to the people
that made it great.
Sounds like the Reyes family's
rubbing off a little bit
on Jenny Kord. no?
Kord has a lot to learn
from the Edge Keys.
Starting with you. Rudy.
Wait a minute.
did you tell her to say that?
Rudy. I didn't say shit.
That sounds like something that
you would say to her to tell me.
And don't worry. Kord Industries
will fix and give you back
your house.
Excuse me.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Here. Rudy.
- What's this?
I felt really bad.
so I got you a new tailgate.
How do you like that. cupcake?
Oh! Wow. it's blue.
A little on the nose. no?
- Rudy.
- Rudy. "Thank you."
- I'll think about it.
- Yeah. take a look.
- Oh. wow. Come on. help me like it.
- I'm inheriting that.
All right. I gotta go.
Yeah.
How about I walk you out?
- Yeah. sure.
- Okay.
So. uh...
when am I gonna see you again?
Soon. I hope.
Where are you headed?
To my dad's.
I want to look at
my mom's paintings again.
I forgot how beautiful they are.
Cool. cool.
Uh...
What if I gave you a ride?
How?
I feel a surge of blood
rushing towards your mid-region.
Stop!
No. no. no. Not you.
Oh.
What's it saying?
Nothing.
Okay.
Hold on.
♪ I'm all out of love.
What am I without you? ♪
♪ I can't be too late
I know I was so wrong ♪
♪ I'm all out of love.
I'm so lost without you ♪
Hello. hello?
Oh. my God. it's working.
Okay. Um...
Whoever turned on my computer.
get a message
to my daughter. Jenny.
Jenny Kord.
Please.
tell her that I love her.
and that I'm sorry.
and her dad is alive.
Ted Kord is alive.
Oh. that's sexy.
www  .  OpenSubtitles  .  org